hotelstravel.com 2018-08-06

# About Us - HotelsTravel.com

### Please provide us with the nature of your question:  

* * *

HotelsTravel.com has been providing discount hotels and other travel-related services to the online community since 1995. We provide over 75,000 links, making ours the most complete, comprehensive and up-to-date hotel directory on the web. 

We're working overtime to provide you with the best prices on the web, for best hotels in the world. After all, your next trip is worth it. 

Sincerely, 

The Team at HotelsTravel.com  
99 West Hawthorne Ave   
Suite 420  
Valley Stream, NY, US 11580 

* * *

This Privacy Policy applies to HotelsTravel.com, (the "website"). 

**What This Privacy Policy Covers:**  
This policy covers how we treat personal information that we collect and receive, including information related to your use of our products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. Of course, this policy only applies to the practices of this website and not to websites that we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage. 

**Why We Have A Privacy Policy**  
We take your privacy very seriously.   
We believe that you should understand how we use the information you provide and furthermore that you should have the right to approve the use of that information. 

**Normal Website Usage**  
You may visit the website to access travel-related information, without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information. The only data we collect and store during normal website usage is typical web server log data. Examples of this type of data are: the name of your Internet service provider, the site that referred you to us, any pages you request, and the time and date of those requests etc. We do not collect any unique information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information.

We use this information to generate statistics and measure site activity to benefit the website users. This same information may be shared with third parties in order to provide these services or to analyze, store, or aggregate the information. It may also be shared with other third parties, working with us to improve our products and services, or this website.   
We want you to get the most out of the website and to trust that we make every effort to protect your confidentiality. Personal information is either requested or required on many areas of the website, to verify your identity and ensure that you qualify to use particular sections of the site. The amount and type of information received depends on how you use our site. The information may be stored and used in order to enhance our relationship with you.

Collection, Use and Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information In using the varied features of the website, you may provide information (such as name, contact information, or other registration information) to us or to our service providers, or other businesses you contact through the use of the website. We and these entities may use, (and you agree to such use) this information and technical information about your use of this web site, or communicate separately with you.   
We will use your information (including your personal information) for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

We may share information about you with our advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. However, we only divulge aggregate information about our users and will not share your personal information with any third party without your express consent. We will not disclose your personal information, except as described herein, and we will not disclose information to others that would connect any personal information with your actual identity unless we are compelled to by law. In our sole discretion we still reserve the right to make exceptions, whenever we believe an emergency, illegal activity or some other reasonable basis exists for notifying or disclosing your personal information to the appropriate authorities. Also, we reserve the right to disclose your personal information to any potential purchaser of our business. 

**Cookies**  
In addition, we may place information on your computer in the form of "cookies" to customize your experience the website. A "cookie" is a small line of text that is stored within your browser when you visit a cookie-enabled website. As you browse the Web, cookie-enabled sites will send cookies to your browser, along with pages. Your browser probably has options that will let you control whether the browser accepts cookies, rejects cookies, or notifies you each time a cookie is sent to you.

If your browser is set to reject cookies, cookie-enabled websites will not recognize you when you return. This provides you with anonymity, but it also makes it very difficult to offer you customized services. It is also less secure than using cookies, because all of your specific data must be sent to the website each time you view a page. Accepting cookies means your private data can stay at the Web server, and the only information transmitted over the Internet is your ID cookie.   
If your browser is set to accept cookies, any cookies that are sent to your browser are stored in your computer for a period of time. There are a few different types of cookies. A "session" cookie is stored only in your computer's working memory (RAM) and only lasts for your browsing session. When you close all of your browser's windows, or when you shut down your computer, the session cookie disappears forever. A "permanent" cookie is stored on your computer's hard drive until a specified date, which could be tomorrow, next week, or 10 years from now. Permanent cookies stay on your computer until either they expire, they are overwritten with newer cookies, or you manually remove them. 

**Unsubscribe Policy**   
If we send you any electronic newsletters, you may unsubscribe at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of every newsletter. 

**Privacy Statement Revisions**  
A revised privacy statement will only apply to data collected subsequent to its effective date on this version of the web site. Any revisions will be posted at least 7 days prior to its effective date. New versions of this website may have a new privacy statement effective with its launch.
